It's hot, isn't it?
暑いよね
hot.
暑い
thank you.
ありがとう
It's kind of nice, something like this.
なんかいいね、こういうの
Your outfit today is cute.
今日の服装可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとう
I like the sandy beach and it's quiet.
砂浜いいね、静かで
That's amazing.
すごいね
I mean, it's spacious.
広いね、っていうか
It's spacious.
広いよね
If there's somewhere I can sit, I'd like to.
なんかどこか座れるとこあったら座りたいけどね
I agree.
そうだね
Shall we go over there?
あっちの方行ってみようか
So let's sit here.
じゃあここ座ろう
Super beautiful.
超きれい
Shizuru-chan.
しずるちゃんが
I?
私が?
Not a great view?
見晴らしじゃなく?
Both.
どっちも
good.
よ かった
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
Good.
よかったよ
What is this?
これ何?
I made a bento today.
今日弁当作ってきたの
Seriously?
マジで?
Why bother?
わざわざ?
Yeah.
うん
But it's not a big deal at all.
でも全然大したものじゃないけど
What what what?
何何何?
Look.
見して
What kind of food did you make?
どんなの作ってくれたの?
Not at all.
全然ね
Well then.
じゃーん
You can eat a lot.
いっぱい食べれるよ
What what what?
何何何?
eat?
食べる?
i want to eat.
食べたい
Let's eat, let's eat.
食べよう食べよう
I haven't eaten anything yet today.
今日まだ何も食べてない
Really?
本当に?
Red food, blue food, and yellow food.
赤の食べ物と 青の食べ物と 黄色の食べ物で
Seriously?
マジ?
It's a traffic light.
信号機じゃん
nutrition.
栄養
nutritional balance.
栄養バランス
Have you completed all types?
全種類コンプリートしちゃった?
That's right.
そうだよ
This is important.
これが大事なんだよ
Looks really delicious.
めっちゃ美味しそう
You just ate your finger too.
今指も食べたでしょ
sorry.
ごめん
I just ate my finger.
今指食べちゃった
sorry.
ごめん
What now?
何今の?
picture?
え?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
恥ずかしい
Was it delicious?
美味しかった?
It was delicious.
美味しかった
Let's make it again.
また作ろう
Is it okay?
いいの?
Let's come again.
また来ようね
I feel sorry.
ごめんと思って
Let's go over there next time.
今度あっちの方行ってみようよ
Let's go.
行ってみよう
it was fun.
楽しかった
It was fun.
楽しかったね
I'm starting to feel sleepy.
なんか眠くなってきた
Are you getting sleepy?
眠くなってきた?
Seriously?
マジ?
Then go to sleep.
じゃあ寝てて
Well then, let's go.
じゃあ行くね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This position.
この体勢
It's hard to touch.
触りづらいな
copper?
どう?
Okay.
いいよ
It's getting hot.
熱くなってきた
Because it's hot.
熱いから
I think I'll eat it because it's hot.
熱いから食べそう
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
This mask.
このマスクね
cool.
涼しい
A lot.
だいぶね
Sweat, I love sweat.
汗、汗好きなの
I like sweat.
汗好きだ
I was covered in sweat.
汗くっついた
While licking me.
俺の舐めながらさ
It was really wet.
めちゃくちゃ濡れてたじゃん
Maybe he's sleeping.
寝てるかも
Did your breasts feel good?
おっぱい気持ちよかった?
what?
なに?
Don't you understand already?
もう分かってない?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Is it easy to feel?
感じやすい?
Easy to touch.
触れやすい
easy to touch
Na.
な
So, you were in a difficult position in the car earlier.
じゃあ さっき車の中で 難しい体勢だったじゃん
Do you like being able to drink?
飲めるの好き?
Yeah.
うん
Wow.
うーわ
It closed soon.
すぐ閉まってきた
That's sneaky.
ずるいじゃん
I went there for the second time.
2回目行ったよね
I want you to feel good too.
俺も気持ちよくしてほしい
But that's okay.
でもいいよ
I wish I could go back.
戻れてたいんだよ
Isn't it easy?
楽でしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Let's go home, then.
帰ろうよ、その後
i got you?
見つけた?
Yeah.
うん
Does contact with the department hurt?
学科の接触で 痛いの?
My stomach growls.
お腹が鳴る
Lick it underneath.
下でペロペロして
Something
なんか
there were.
あ った
What should I do?
どうする?
I told my favorite story.
好きな話にした
this.
これ
It's just the tip though.
先っぽだけど
Like Sue-chan, I also have sensitive nipples.
スーちゃんみたいに 俺も乳首弱いから
Do you have it?
持ってるかな?
Looks like it's going to fall.
落ちそう
It'll be on top.
上になるじゃん
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
You're sneaky, will you be on top?
ずるいじゃん、上になる?
Will it be on top?
上になる?
My butt is embarrassing.
お尻恥ずかしいな
Isn't it a cute butt?
可愛いお尻でしょ?
soft.
柔らかい
I laughed.
笑いちゃった
Quiet.
安静
Who is this?
なんか誰?
sperm.
精子
I'll take a shower and try again.
シャワー浴びてもう一回するじゃん
シャワー浴びてもう一回じゃん
Don't say anything embarrassing.
恥ずかしいこと言わないで
I was writing work.
仕事書いてたじゃん
Don't say it.
言わないで
Because I'm doing it while saying it.
言いながらやってるから
I just said it.
言 ったばかり
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
amazing?
すごい?
I feel like I'll be able to put it in soon.
すぐ入れそうな感じだけど
Because you're standing there.
そこに立ってるんだから
Is it a toothpaste?
お歯付けなの?
No, I want to put it in right away.
いや、すぐ入れたい
I want to put it in right away.
すぐに入れたい
Okay.
いいよ
You can also wear teeth.
お歯付けでもいいよ
Is it okay to wear teeth?
お歯付けでいい?
There are a lot of them.
多いんだもん
My lower back also hurts.
腰も痛い
Do you want coffee?
コーヒーする?
coffee?
コ ーヒー?
delicious?
おいしい?
A little salty.
ちょっとしょっぱい
Salty?
しょっぱい?
thumb?
親指?
same?
同じ?
Bodizoff taste?
ボディーゾーフの味?
I hadn't washed it properly.
ちゃんと洗ってなかった
Isn't it because you washed it properly?
ちゃんと洗ったからじゃないの?
Arf.
アーフね
delicious?
おいしい?
I feel weird.
変な感じしてる
Expect to be licked like before.
さっきみたいに舐められるの期待してね
believe?
信じる?
Is it a cheap doctor?
安い医師かな?
Is that the one from Suzu-chan?
スズウちゃん出したやつかな?
Isn't that the one from Suzu-chan?
スズウちゃん出したやつじゃない?
Can you join me for a drink?
一緒に飲みながら飲んでくれる?
Yeah.
うん
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
Because it's good.
うまいから
Because Suzu-chan is a good blowjob.
スズウちゃんのフェラーうまいから
Even if I served it twice, there was soba.
2回出してもそばがあって
Yeah.
うん
good?
うまい?
This way.
こっち
stomach
い
It comes out a lot.
っぱ い出てくる